50  这个数字是Android应用市场Google Play
50. That's how many apps were available in
随着第一款Android设备的发布  在2008年推出时
Android Market as Google Play was named when
它所拥有的应用程序的数量
it first launched alongside the first Android device
在几天之后  Android应用市场
in 2008. A few days later, Android Market
向所有的开发者开放注册并且
opened for all app developers to register and
在没有任何来自Google OEM厂商
start publishing their apps without any review or
或运营商的审查和验证情况下  就开始发布他们的应用程序
validation requirements from Google, OEMs, or carriers. For
我们作为一个开发者  发布应用的可能性
us as developers, the ability to distribute apps and
和通过应用中支付以及直接把广告推向
the possibility of monetizing them through up front payments
超过10亿的Android设备用户等途径进行盈利
in app billing and advertising directly to the owners of
的可能性  是Android生态系统
over a billion android devices is one of the
提供的最激动人心的机会之一
most exciting opportunities made possible by the android ecosystem. Growing
在我成长的没有智能手机和互联网的年代
up the dark days before smartphones and the internet,
如果我想要一款新的游戏或者应用程序
if I wanted a new game or app I had
我不得不去实体店购买
to go to a physical store and pay for a
盒装的软盘或者光盘  作为开发者
cardboard box filled with floppy disks or CDROMs. As developers
当时我们商业计划的很大一部分是
a big part of our business plan back then
如何把我们软件的包装盒放到那些货架上
was how to get those boxes of our software onto
或者在移动设备的世界中  如何
those shelves. Or in the world of mobile, how
让运营商或OEM厂商和我们达成协议
to secure a carrier or OEM deal to get our
把我们的应用程序预装到设备上  今天我可以安装
apps preloaded onto the devices. Today I can install
一百多万个  不是由成百上千的而是只有几十开发者开发的
over a million apps or games created by tens if
通过Google Play提供的应用程序或游戏
not hundreds and thousands of developers via Google Play, all
只需要点击一个按钮即可完成  那将是上百亿的
with a click of a button. That's translated into tens
应用程序安装量  是一个将应用程序发布到数百个国家
of billions of app installs. An incredible opportunity to
中的Android用户中的难以置信的机会
distribute apps to Android users in hundreds of countries.
在Android发展的早期  快速开发
Now, in the early days of Android, being fast
第一个发布程序是一个相当坚实的成功的策略
and launching first was a pretty solid strategy for success,
但是随着开始的50个应用程序迅速地增长到
but as those first 50 apps quickly grew to
上百  上千  甚至是现在超过一百万的应用程序
hundreds, thousands, and now over a million apps, it takes
需要在应用中脱颖而出成为佼佼者需要的不仅仅是速度
a lot more than speed to stand out from
现在  应用的品质事关重大
the crowd. These days the tables stakes are a base
你需要愿意为你所有的用户创造
line of quality and willingness to create great experiences
优秀的用户体验  当然应用的质量是
for all your users. Of course app quality can
具有主观性的  但是多年来我们已经确定了
be somewhat subjective, but over the years we've identified
用户辨别一个应用是否为高质量应用的核心标准
the core criteria that users identify with apps of
为了让你不用浪费精力
high quality. And to make your life easier, they're
它们已经在Android开发者网站上供你浏览了
all available on the Android developer site for you
这份清单也是Google Play的销售团队
to review. This is the same checklist that the
用来确保只有高质量的应用
merchandising team for Google Play used to ensure only apps
才会被他们推荐并且出现在
of quality are featured in their promotions and
商店的编辑推荐板块  清单包括了所有方面  从遵循
editor's choice categories. And they include everything, from following
应用设计指南到支持不同的屏幕方向
the app design guidelines to supporting different screen orientations,
平板和其他设备  当然还要确保
tablets, and other devices. And of course ensuring that
你的应用程序的稳定性和高性能
your app is stable and performant. So, with over
所以  在Google Playyi已经有超过一百万的应用程序
a million apps already available in Google Play it's
我们现在不仅仅是玩数字游戏了  我们不只是需要
no longer just a numbers game. We don't need
更多的应用和游戏  甚至更多的开发者
just more apps or games, or even more developers.
我们所需要的是像你一样的优秀的开发者开发出来的高质量的应用程序
What we want is high quality apps from great developers, like you.